Guide to the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association records, circa 1800-2022 MS2027
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Images, Circa 1960-Circa 1998; MS2027 Series 1
  - People feeding ducks along the canal, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 179)
    Text on photograph: "Ducks get a handout mile 14"
  - Bluebells along the towpath, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 180)
    Text with photograph: "Bluebells on the towpath mile 95"
  - Trout lillies by towpath, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 181)
    Text with photograph: "Trout lilies by Towpath mile 96"
  - Red trillium, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 182)
    Text on photograph: "Red Trillium mile 96"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Association booth, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 183)
  - Natural landscape, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 184)
  - Sign for McCoy's Ferry, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 185)
  - Lockhouse at Lock 68, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 186)
    Text with photograph: "Lockhouse at Lock 68 mile 165"
  - Fish trap on Potomac River, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 187)
    Text with photograph: "Fish trap on Potomac River mile 133"
  - Two men and a goat on the towpath, Circa 1985 (Box 26, Folder 188)
    Text with photograph: "You meet the most interesting people on the Towpath!"
  - Photographs from other repositories, undated (Box 26, Folder 189)
    Photographs by Jack Rottier and National Park Service
  - 14th Annual Reunion preparation, 1968 April 27 (Box 26, Folder 190)
    Photographs by National Park Service
    - 14th Annual Reunion preparation, 1968 April 27; Item 1
      Caption: "Chesapeake and Ohio Canal Association--14th Annual Reunion Saturday, April 27, 1968. Early spring reconnaissance of the route of hte 14th Annual Renion HIke of the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal Association. Left to right: Robert W. Bell, Chief of Interpretation, C. & O. Canal National Monument; Colin Ritter, Reunion Chairman; and W. Dean McClannahan, Superintendent, Chesapeake and Ohio Canal National Monument. This year's hike starts at Weverton, Md., Lock 31, with a lunch stop at Antietam Creek Camping Area, and terminates at the Rumsey Bridge across the Potomac from Shepardstown, W. Virginia..."
  - Congressman Gilbert Gude - Canoeing, Circa 1966 (Box 26, Folder 191)
    Photograph by the Washington Post Company
  - Potomac River at Seneca Basin/Pool, undated (Box 26, Folder 192)
    Photographs by the National Park Service
  - Potomac River at Hancock, MD, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 193)
    Photograph by National Park Service
  - Potomac River at Great Falls, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 194)
  - Potomac River at Goose Creek, Va, undated (Box 26, Folder 195)
    Photograph taken by National Park Service
  - White's Ferry, Circa 1960 (Box 26, Folder 196)
    Photograph taken by the National Park Service
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal towpath, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 1)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Towpath Hike 4-25-64 IPAVEC"
  - People walking on the Chesapeake & Ohio Canal towpath, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 2)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Towpath 4-25-64 IPAVEC"
  - People resting along Chesapeake & Ohio Canal towpath, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 3)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Towpath 4-25-64 IPAVEC"
  - People resting along Chesapeake & Ohio Canal towpath, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 4)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike Towpath 4-25-64 IPAVEC"
  - People resting along Chesapeake & Ohio Canal towpath, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 5)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Towpath 4-35-64 IPAVEC"
  - People along Chesapeake & Ohio Canal towpath, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 6)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Towpath 4-35-64 IPAVEC"
  - People along Chesapeake & Ohio Canal towpath, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 7)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal 4-25-64 IPAVEC"
  - W. O. Douglas at Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 8)
    Text on slide: "W. O. Douglas Chesapeake & Ohio Canal 4-25-64 IPAVEC"
  - People at Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 9)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal 4-25-64 IPAVEC"
  - People hiking along Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 10)
  - People at Chesapeake & Ohio Canal at Little Orleans, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 11)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal (LT. Orleans) 4-25-64 IPAVEC"
  - People at Chesapeake & Ohio Canal at Little Orleans, 1964 April 25 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 12)
    Text on slides: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal (LT. Orleans) 4-25-64 IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal hike at Little Orleans, 1964 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 13)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike Little Orleans Apr. 64 IPAVEC"
  - House at Lock 72, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 14)
    Text on slide: "Lock #72 & House Chesapeake & Ohio Canal 6-65 IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 15)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal 6-65 Oldtown, MD. IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Long's house at Lock 68, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 17)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal 6-65 Long's House @ Lock #68 Oldtown IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Aqueduct, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 18)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal 6-65 IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Potomac River, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 20)
    Text on slide: "Potomac River (Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike 6-65) IPAVEC"
  - Sideling Hill Aqueduct, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 21)
    Text on slide: "Sideling Hill Aqueduct 6-65 IPAVEC"
  - Sideling Creek, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 22)
    Text on slide: "Sideling Creek (Beaver) 6-65 IPAVEC"
  - Dam #6 at Potomac River, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 23)
    Text on slide: "Dam #6 - Potomac R. 6-65 IPAVEC"
  - Wild roses, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 24)
    Text on slide: "Wild Roses - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal (Hancock) 6-65 IPAVEC"
  - Wheat field, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 25)
    Text on slide: "Wheat Field (Hancock) 6-65 IPAVEC"
  - Natural landscape, 1965 June (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 26)
    Text on slide: "Hancock, MD. 6-65 IPAVEC"
  - People at White's Ferry, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 27)
    Text on photograph: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal White's Ferry 4-66"
  - Justice Douglas and others, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 28)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Douglas 4-66 IPAVEC"
  - People at Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 29)
    Text on slides: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Udall 4-66 IPAVEC"
  - People at Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 30)
    Text on slides: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal 4-66 IPAVEC"
  - Bluebells, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 31)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Bluebells 4-66 IPAVEC"
  - People at Edwards Ferry, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 32)
    Text on slides: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Edwards Ferry 4-66 IPAVEC"
  - Edwards Ferry, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 33)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Edwards Ferry 4-66 IPAVEC"
  - Edwards Ferry, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 34)
  - People at Edwards Ferry, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 35)
  - People at Edwards Ferry, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 36)
  - People at Edwards Ferry, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 37)
  - People at Edwards Ferry, 1966 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike, 1968 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 39)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike Weverton, MD. 4-68 IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike approaching Harpers Ferry, 1968 April 27 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 40)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike 4-27-68 approaching Harpers Ferry IPAVEC"
  - Justice and Cathy Douglas, 1968 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 41)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike Justice & Cathy Douglas 4-68 IPAVEC"
  - Feeder Dam #3 at Potomac River, 1968 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 42)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike Potomac - Feeder Dam #3 IPAVEC"
  - Antietam Creek Aqueduct, 1968 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 43)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike 4-68 Antietam Aqueduct IPAVEC"
  - Antietam Creek picnic area, 1968 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 44)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike 4-68 Antietam Creek Picnic Area IPAVEC"
  - Antietam Creek picnic area, 1968 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 45)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike 4-68 Antietam Picnic Area"
  - Army trucks at the end of Chesapeake & Ohio Canal hike, 1968 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 46)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike 4-68 Shepherdstown, W. Va. Army trucks at end of hike IPAVEC"
  - Harpers Ferry, 1968 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 47)
    Text on slide: "Harpers Ferry 4-68 IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 48)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike 4/70 Seneca IPAVEC"
  - Man with opossom, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 49)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Seneca 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - People, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 50)
  - People, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Natural landscape, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 52)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - Toby Town welcome, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 53)
    Text on slide: "Toby Town Welcome Chesapeake & Ohio 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - Toby Town welcome, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 54)
    Text on slide: "Toby Town Welcome Chesapeake & Ohio 4/70"
  - Toby Town welcome, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Toby Town welcome, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 56)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Toby Town 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - People, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 57)
  - People, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Hike, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 59)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Hike 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - People hiking along Pennyfield Lock, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 60)
    Text on slide: "Pennyfield Lock Chesapeake & Ohio 4/70"
  - Pennyfield Lock, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 61)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Pennyfield 4/60 IPAVEC"
  - Pennyfield Lock, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Great Falls of Potomac River, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 63)
    Text on slide: "Great Falls 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - Great Falls of Potomac River, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 64)
    Text on slides: "Great Falls 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - Great Falls of Potomac River, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 65)
    Text on slide: "Great Falls of Potomac (Chesapeake & Ohio) 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - Great Falls of Potomac River, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 66)
    Text on slide: "Great Falls of Potomac Chesapeake & Ohio 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - Great Falls of Potomac River, 1970 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 67)
    Text on slide: "Great Falls Chesapeake & Ohio 4/70 IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike, 1971 May 01 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 68)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike 5/1/71 IPAVEC"
  - Lock 72, 1971 May 01 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 69)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike Lock 72 5/1/71 IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal Hike, 1971 May 01 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 70)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Hike 5/1/71 IPAVEC"
  - Apple Blossoms, 1971 May 01 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 71)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Hike 5/1/71 Apple Blossoms IPAVEC"
  - Chesapeake & Ohio Canal hike approaching Cumberland, 1971 May 01 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 72)
    Text on slides: "Chesapeake & Ohio Hike 5/1/71 Approaching Cumberland IPAVEC"
  - Conococheague Creek Aqueduct, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 73)
    Text on slide: "72 Chesapeake & Ohio Conococheaque"
  - Conococheague Creek Aqueduct, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 74)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 72 Conococheaque IPAVEC"
  - Conococheague Creek Aqueduct, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 75)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 72 Conococheague IPAVEC"
  - People, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 76)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 72 Crowder, Cathy & WOD IPAVEC"
  - People, 1971 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 77)
    Text on slide: " '72 Conococheaque D. Ipavec, D. Greene, Hooper Wolfe IPAVEC"
  - Flowers, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 78)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 72 IPAVEC"
  - Bluebells, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 79)
    Text on slide: "Bluebells Chesapeake & Ohio '72"
  - Bluebells, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 80)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Bluebells '72 IPAVEC"
  - Red Trillium, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 81)
    Text on slide: "Red Trillium 72 Chesapeake & Ohio IPAVEC"
  - Red Trillium, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 82)
  - Nodding Star of Bethlehem, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 83)
    Text on slide: "Nodding Star of Bethlehem 72 IPAVEC"
  - Natural landscape, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 84)
  - Natural landscape, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 85)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Mustard '72 IPAVEC"
  - Natural landscape, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 86)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Mustard '72 IPAVEC "
  - Bluebells, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 87)
    Text on slide: "72 Chesapeake & Ohio Bluebells IPAVEC"
  - Near Falling Waters, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 88)
    Text on slide: "72 Chesapeake & Ohio Near Falling Waters IPAVEC"
  - Potomac River, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 89)
    Text on slide: "Potomac '72 IPAVEC"
  - Natural landscape, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 90)
    Text on slide: "72 Chesapeake & Ohio IPAVEC"
  - Towpath flowers, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 91)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Towpath flowers '72 IPAVEC"
  - Star of Bethlehem, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 92)
    Text on slide: "72 Chesapeake & Ohio Star of Bethlehem IPAVEC"
  - Violets, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 93)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Violets 72 IPAVEC"
  - Spring Beauty (flowers), 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 94)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Spring Beauty 72 IPAVEC"
  - Dutchman's Breeches (flowers), 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 95)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Dutchman's Breeches 72 IPAVEC"
  - Swan at Big Pool, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 96)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Swan '72 Big Pool"
  - Licking Creek Aqueduct, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 97)
    Text on slide: "72 Chesapeake & Ohio Licking Creek Aqueduct IPAVEC"
  - Licking Creek Aqueduct, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 98)
  - Licking Creek Aqueduct, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 99)
  - Licking Creek Aqueduct, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 100)
  - Licking Creek Aqueduct, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 101)
  - Licking Creek Aqueduct, 1972 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 102)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 72 Licking Creek Aqueduct IPAVEC"
  - Aqueduct, 1973 (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 103)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio '73 Aqueduct IPAVEC"
  - Mayapple (plant), 1973 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 104)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Mayapple 5/73 IPAVEC"
  - Licking Creek Aqueduct, 1973 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 105)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 5/73 IPAVEC"
  - Footbridge at Little Pool, 1973 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 27, Folder 106)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 5/73 Footbridge - Little Pool IPAVEC"
  - Buildings in natural landscape, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 1)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Trail down natural landscape, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 2)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 4/74 Redbud IPAVEC"
  - Natural landscape, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 3)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Redbud 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Building, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Salty Dog Saloon, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 5)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Salty Dog Saloon 4/74 Harpers Ferry IPAVEC"
  - Catoctin Creek Aqueduct Repair, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 6)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 4/74 Catoctin Aqueduct Repair IPAVEC"
  - Catoctin Creek Aqueduct Repair, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 7)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 4/74 Catoctin Aqueduct IPAVEC"
  - Catoctin Creek Aqueduct and ferry, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 8)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 4/74 Catoctin Creek Ferry IPAVEC"
  - Catoctin Creek Aqueduct, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 9)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Catoctin Creek Aqueduct 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Catoctin Creek Aqueduct and ferry, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 10)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Catoctin Creek Ferry 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Catoctin Creek Aqueduct and ferry, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Catoctin Creek Ferry, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Catoctin Creek Ferry, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Garlic Mustard (plant), 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 14)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Garlic Mustard 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Monocacy Aqueduct, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 15)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Monocacy Aqueduct 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Monocacy Aqueduct, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Monocacy Aqueduct, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Natural landscape, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 21)
  - People walking along canal, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 22)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 4/74 Ken Rollins IPAVEC"
  - PEPCO Plant, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 23)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio PEPCO Plant 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - PEPCO Plant, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Natural landscape, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Woods Lock, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 26)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Woods Lock No. 26 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Woods Lock, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 27)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Woods Lock No. 26 4/74 IPAEC"
  - Flowers, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 28)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Phlox 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Whites Ferry, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 29)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Whites Ferry 4/74 A. IPAVEC"
  - Whites Ferry, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 30)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio White's Ferry 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Whites Ferry, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 31)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Whites Ferry 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Great Falls Water Supply Dam, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 32)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Great Falls Water Supply Dam 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Flowers, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Flowers, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Natural landscape, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 35)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Dogwood 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Towpath, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 36)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Towpath at Seneca 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Protesters, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 37)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Protesters at Seneca 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Natural landscape, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 38)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Great Falls to Seneca 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Natural landscape, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Great Falls Tavern, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 40)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Great Falls Tavern 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Natural landscape, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Rocks Below Great Falls, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 42)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Rocks Below Great Falls 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Picnic, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 43)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Above Sycamore Island 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Hand Ferry to Sycamore Island, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 44)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Hand Ferry to Sycamore Island 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Lock 6, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 45)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Lock 6 (HAHNS) 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Lock 6, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Lock 6, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 47)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Lock No. 6 (Hahns') 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Lock 6, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 48)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Lock No. 6 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Lock 6, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 49)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio Lock No. 6 (Parkers) 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Men walking, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 50)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio 4/74 (Grant Conway) IPAVEC"
  - Natural landscape-canal, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 51)
  - People at the end of a hike, 1974 April (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 52)
    Text on slide: "Chesapeake & Ohio - End of Hike Chris Parker 4/74 IPAVEC"
  - Man carrying tree branches, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Woman carrying tree branch, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Cityscape, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 55)
  - People fixing fence, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 56)
  - People cleaning, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Man raking, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Man cleaning, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 59)
  - "The Georgetown" boat in canal, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Man cleaning around aqueduct, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 61)
  - Women carrying pieces of brush, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 62)
  - People cleaning, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 63)
  - People, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 64)
  - Cityscape, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 65)
  - People cleaning, 1983 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Box 28, Folder 66)
  - People cleaning, 1986 May (Box SHARED Box 12, Folder 28, Folder 67)